Collection of Motion Picture Pressbooks PASC.0248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Indestructible Man, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Inside the Mafia, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Interiors, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Intermezzo, no date (Box 19, Folder 14)
- International Crime, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Invasion of the Body Snatchers, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Investigation of a Citizen Above Suspicion, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Ipcress File (The), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Island Of Terror (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Italiano Brava Gente, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- It's Alive, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Ivanhoe, no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Jail Busters, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Jalopy, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Jaws, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Jazz on a Summer's Day, no date (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Jenny, no date (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Jezebel, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Julia, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Julie the Redhead, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Julius Caesar, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Jungle Book (The), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Jungle Gents, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Just Squaw, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Kangroo, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Khamishia- Five Tales from Israel, no date (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Kids are Alright (The), no date (Box 12, Folder 14)
- King Kong, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- King of The Gypsies, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- King of the Stallions, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Kliou the Killer, no date (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Klute, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kramer vs. Kramer, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- La Femme Infidele, no date (Box 1, Folder 33)
- La Guerre Est Finie, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Lady Ice, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Lady Luck, no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Land That Time Forgot (The), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Lasca, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Last American Hero (The), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Last Days of Pompeii (The), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Last Detail (The), 1974 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Last of the Desperados, no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Last Summer, no date (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Last Survivor (The), 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Last Tycoon (The), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Last Valley (The), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Last Valley (The), 1971 (Box Unknown container 918 for instance of Last Valley (The))
- Last Waltz (The), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Last Wave (The), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Late Show (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Lawless Woman (The), no date (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Lawrence of Arabia, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Leadbelly, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Leech Woman (The), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Lenny, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Lesson In Love (A), no date (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Let the Good Times Roll, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Lies My Father Told Me, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Life in Danger, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Lifeguard, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Lifeguard, circa 1975 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Light in the Forest (The), 1958 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Lightning Strikes West, no date (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Lili, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Lili, no date (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Limelight, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Lion in Winter (The), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Lipstick, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Lipstick, no date (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Lisztomania, no date (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Little Big Man, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Little Darlings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Little Girl Who Lives Down the Lane (The), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Little Laura and Big John, no date (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Little Murders, no date (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Little Night Music (A), no date (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Lively Set (The), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Lock Up Your Daughters, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Logan's Run, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Lola, circa 1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Lola Montes, no date (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Looking for Danger, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Looking for Mr. Goodbar, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Lord of the Rings (The), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Love and Anarchy, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Love and Kisses, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Love At First Bite, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Love is News, no date (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Loved One (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Lovemaker (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Lovers and Other Strangers, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Lovers of Paris, no date (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Loves Of Isadora (The), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Lucky Lady, no date (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Ludwig, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Lumiere, no date (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Lumiere, no date (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Lumiere, no date (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Luna, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Machine Gun McCain, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Macon County Line, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Mad About Music, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Madam Kitty, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Magic, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Mahler, no date (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Main Event (The), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Malibu Beach, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Man (The), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Man and a Woman (A), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Man Between (The), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Man Called Dagger (A), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Man Escaped (A), no date (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Man from Tumbleweeds (The), no date (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Man in the Mirror (The), no date (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Man of the East, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Man on a Swing, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Maniac, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Marathon Man, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Martin, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Marty, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Massacre in Rome, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Matchless, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- McCabe and Mrs. Miller, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- McQ, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Meatballs, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Meetings with Remarkable Men, no date (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Midnight Cowboy, no date (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Midnight Express, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Mind of Mr. Soames (The), 1970 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Minnesota Clay, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Misadventures of Merlin Jones (The), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Missouri Breaks (The), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Mistress (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Mondo Topless, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Money Trap (The), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Monkey's Uncle (The), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Monsieur Verdoux, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Monty Python and the Holy Grail, no date (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Moon Pilot, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Moonraker, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Mother and the Whore (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Mother, Jugs (A)nd Speed, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Mr. Mike's Mondo Video, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Mrs. Brown, You've Got a Lovely Daughter, no date (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Mrs. Slacker, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Muppet Movie (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Murder By Death, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Murder By Death, no date (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Murder on the Orient Express, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Music Lovers (The), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Mustang Country, no date (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Mutations (The), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- My Brilliant Career, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- My Brilliant Career, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- My Son, My Son, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- My Tutor, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Mysterious Crossing, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Naked Jungle (The), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Naked Prey (The), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Naked Runner (The), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Naked Under Leather, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Name of the Game is Kill! (The), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Namu, the Killer Whale, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Nashville, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Nashville Girl, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Nasty Habits, no date (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Navy Blue and Gold, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Nea, no date (Box 5, Folder 30)
- New Centurions (The)/Five Easy Pieces, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- New York Nights, no date (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Night Cargo, no date (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Night Encounter, no date (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Nights of Cabiria, no date (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Night of the Generals (The), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Night of the Living Dead, no date (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Night of the Shooting Stars, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Night They Raided Minsky's (The), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Nikki Wild Dog of the North, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Nikki, Wild Dog of the North, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Nine Ages of Nakedness, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Nine Lives of Fritz the Cat, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- No Deposit No Return, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- No Holds Barred, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- No Time for Breakfast, no date (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Norma Rae, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Norma Rae, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Nosferatu, no date (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Nothing Sacred, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- O Lucky Man!, no date (Box 9, Folder 51)
- O. S. S. 117 is Not Dead, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Obsession, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Odd Couple (The), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Ode To Billy Joe, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Odyssey (The), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Of Human Bondage, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Office Scandal (The), no date (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Oh, God, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Oklahoman (The), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Omen (The), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- On a Clear Day You Can See Forever, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Once in Paris, no date (Box 10, Folder 10)
- One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, no date (Box 8, Folder 39)
- One Million B.C., no date (Box 8, Folder 17)
- One of Our Dinosaurs is Missing, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- One-Trick Pony, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- One Way Trail, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Operation Disaster, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Operation Eichmann, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Orca, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Other Side of the Mountain (The), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Out of It, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Outside the Wall, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Owl and the Pussycat (The), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Pad (The), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Painted Veil (The), 1935 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Panama Red, no date (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Pardon Mon Affaire, no date (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Parent Trap (The), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Paris Playboys, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Paroled From the Big House, no date (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Passages From James Joyce's Finnegans Wake, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Passenger (The), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Pat Garrett And Billy The Kid, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Pather Panchali, no date (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Paul and Michelle, no date (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Penrod and His Twin Brother, no date (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Percy, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Perfect Friday, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Performance, no date (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Perri, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Pete 'n' Tillie, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Peter Rabbit and Tales of Beatrix Potter, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Pete's Dragon, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Petulia, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Phantom Of The Paradise, no date (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Phasen, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Picnic, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Picnic at Hanging Rock, no date (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Pink Panther Strikes Again (The), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Pioneers of the Frontier, no date (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Piranha, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Play it Again, Sam, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Play It As It Lays, no date (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Play It Cool, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Please Get Married, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Pocketful of Miracles, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Popi, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Poseidon Adventure (The), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Pretty Baby, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Pretty Baby, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Pretty Smooth, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Prime Cut, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Prince and the Pauper (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Prison Train, no date (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Private Eyes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Prodigal Liar (The), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Projected Man (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Promise at Dawn, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Quackser Fortune Has a Cousin in the Bronx, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Quadrophenia, no date (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Queen (The), no date (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Quintet, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- R.P.M., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Rabbit Test, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Rabid, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Radio City Revels, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Rag Man (The), 1925 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Rage of Angels, no date (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Rage of Burlesque (The), circa 1951 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Rainbow Bridge, no date (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Rancho Deluxe, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Rapture, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Rebellious Daughters, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Red Meadows (also known as De Rode Enge), no date (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Reincarnation of Peter Proud (The), no date (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Reivers (The), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Rembrandt, no date (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Rescuers (The), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Restless Natives, no date (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Return of Captain Marvel, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Return of Sabata, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Return of the Man Called Horse (The), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Revenge of the Creature, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Revenge of the Pink Panther, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Revolt of the Zombies, no date (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Ridin' the Trail, no date (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Rio Bravo, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Rio Lobo, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Riot Squad (The), no date (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Ritz (The), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Roadie, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Roadies, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Robin and Marian, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Rock 'n Roll Your Eyes, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Rocky, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Rocky Horror Picture Show (The), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Rod Roy, The Highland Rogue, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Roll Along, Cowboy, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Rollerball, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Rolling Stones, no date (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Rolling Stones (The) - Gimme Shelter, no date (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Roman Scandals, no date (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Roman Spring of Mrs. Stone (The), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Romantic Englishwoman (The), no date (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Romeo and Juliet, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Romeo and Juliet, no date (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Rose (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Rose of the Rancho, no date (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Roseland, no date (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Rosemary's Baby, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Roustabout, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Royal Flash, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Ruling Class (The), no date (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Runaway Hormones, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Runner Stumbles (The), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Rust Never Sleeps, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- S.O.S. Pacific, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- S.O.S. Submarine (also known as Uomini Sul Fondo), no date (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Sabata, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Sacrifice D'Honneur, no date (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Sage Brush Hamlet (A), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Sailor Who Fell from Grace with the Sea (The), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Saint Jack, no date (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Salamandre, La, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Sally, Irene and Mary, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Sammy the way-out seal, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Sandakan 8, no date (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Sandflow, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Santa and the Ice Cream Bunny, no date (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Santee, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Saturday Night Fever, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Savage Eye (The), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Savage Guns (The), 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Savage Messiah, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Savage Sisters, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Savage!, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Save the Children, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Scalawag, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Scarface, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Schlock, no date (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Second Honeymoon, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Secret Door (The), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Secret Partner (The), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Secrets of a Co-Ed, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Seduction of Mimi (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Semi-Tough, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Señor Jim, no date (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Señor Jim, no date (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Serengeti, no date (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Sergeant (The), 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Sergeants 3, no date (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Serial, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Serpico, no date (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Seven Beauties, no date (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Seven Little Foys (The), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Seven Per Cent Solution, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Sex Kittens Go To College, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Sextoons, no date (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Shadow of Fear, no date (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Shadow of the Hawk, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Shadow of the Hawk, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Shadows Over Shanghai, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Shaft in Africa, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Shampoo, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Sheriff of Sage Valley (The), 1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Sheriff's Son (The), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Sherlock Holmes' Smarter Brother, no date (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Ship of Fools, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Shock Corridor, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Shoes of the Fisherman (The), no date (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Shootist (The), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Shout (The), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Sign of Zorro (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Silent Movie, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Silent Witness, no date (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Silver Streak, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Singing Cowgirl (The), 1939 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Sisters, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Skammen Shame, circa 1969 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Skullduggery, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Sky Raiders, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Slander House, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Sleeper, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Sleeping Beauty, no date (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Sleeping Beauty (The), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Slender Thread (The), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Sleuth, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Slim Carter, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Slither, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Small Change, no date (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Smile, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- So Dear to My Heart, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Solaris, no date (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Some Bride, no date (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Son of Sinbad, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Son on Flubber, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Song of Norway, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Sound of Laughter (The), no date (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Speakeasy, no date (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Speed Madness, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Spirits of the Dead, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Spook Chasers, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Spotlight Scandals, no date (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Spy With My Face (The)/To Trap a Spy, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Square Jungle (The), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Square Shoulder, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Squirm, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Stacey!, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Stage Door Canteen, no date (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Star is Born (A), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Star Trek, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Star Wars, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Star Wars, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Starting Over, no date (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Station West, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Steppenwolf, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Stewardesses (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Sting (The), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Stolen Kisses, circa 1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Stone Killer (The), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Stopover: Tokyo, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Story of Adele H. (The), no date (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Straight Time, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Strange Lady, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Strangler (The), no date (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Strawberry Statement (The), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Street People, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Strike Me Pink, no date (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Subject was Roses (The), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Subway in the Sky, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Summer Magic, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Summer School Teachers, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Sunshine Boys (The), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Super Fly T.N.T., no date (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Superman, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Susannah of the Mounties, no date (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Swashbuckler, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Sweet Sweetback's Baadasssss Song, no date (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Swept Away, no date (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Sword in the Stone (The), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Sword of Sherwood Forest, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Take A Girl Like You, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Take The Money and Run, no date (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Taking Off, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Tanks A Million, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Tarantula, no date (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Taste of Beefcake (A), no date (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Taste of Blood (A), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Ten From Your Show of Shows, no date (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Tenderfoot (The), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Terror in the Jungle, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Terrorists (The), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Texas John Slaughter, no date (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Texas Trail, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- That Certain Feeling, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- That Certain Woman, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- That'll be the Day, no date (Box 19, Folder 35)
- There Goes the Groom, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- There's Always Tomorrow, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- They Died with Their Boots On, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, no date (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Things of Life (The), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Third Secret, no date (Box 10, Folder 46)
- This is Russia, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- This Property is Condemned, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Three Lives of Thomasina (The), 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Three Musketeers (The)/Four Musketeers (The), no date (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Thunder Road, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Thunder Trail, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Tilt, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Timelock, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
- TNT Jackson, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Toll of the Desert, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Tomboy and the Champ, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Too Late The Hero, no date (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Top of the Heap, no date (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Torch (The), 1950 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Tormented, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Tovarich, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Towering Inferno, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Train Robbers (The), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Tricia's Wedding, no date (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Triple Irons (also known as Xin Dubi Daowang), no date (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Trouble in the Sky, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Truck Turner, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Turn in the Road (The), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Twins of Evil, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Two Gun Law, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Ugly Dachshund (The), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Umberto D., no date (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Umbrellas of Cherbourg (The), no date (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Un Dejeuner De Soleil, no date (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Underground, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Union Pacific, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Unwed Mother, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Up in Arms, no date (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Up the Junction, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Valerie, no date (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Vampire Bat (The), 1933 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Villain (The), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Virgin and the Gypsy (The), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Virgin Spring (The), no date (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Viva Zapata, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- W.W. and the Dixie Dancekings, no date (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Walking Tall, no date (Box 3, Folder 17)
- War and Peace, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- War Bride's Secret (The), no date (Box 16, Folder 41)
- War of the Satellites, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Warlords of Atlantis, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Warm December (A), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Warm December (A), no date (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Warriors (The), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Way We Were (The), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Web of Evidence, no date (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Weekend Pass, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Well (The), 1951 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- We're in the Legion Now, no date (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Westerner (The), no date (Box 16, Folder 43)